gobza.com 2013-03-23

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

This privacy policy is designed to inform users of the Gobza website (www.gobza.com), mobile applications, microsites, software and service (collectively, the “Service”) about how Tops Global, Inc., doing business as Gobza (“Gobza”, “we” or “us”), gathers and uses personal information collected by us in connection with use of the Service. Gobza will take reasonable steps to protect user privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this policy and with applicable U.S. laws. In this policy, “user” or “you” means any person using the Service, whether by browsing the Gobza website or mobile apps, purchasing a Gobza promotional voucher (“Vouchers”) that may be exchanged for goods and services offered by Gobza merchants (each a “Merchant”), uploading or exchanging a Voucher, or participating in any other activities available through the Service. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THE SERVICE.

**First Up, We Want You to Know This**

We will never disclose your email address to any user (including Merchants) or any other third party for their marketing purposes. This allows you to use Gobza without receiving a whole lot of direct marketing you don't want.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

 _Information You Share_

: Gobza collects some of your personal information in connection with the Service. When you sign up to create a Gobza account, purchase a Voucher, submit content to Gobza, complete a survey, send us feedback, request information about the Service, apply for a job, post a video, or sign up for special offers from third parties, Gobza may collect personal information from you, such as your email address, first and last name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or related information (collectively, “Personal Information”) when you, for example:

  * sign up to create a Gobza account,
  * submit or post content to Gobza,
  * participate in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games or applications,
  * create, or engage in discussions in, forums or message boards,
  * send us feedback or request information about the Service, or
  * sign up for special offers from third parties.

You do not have to provide Personal Information to Gobza, but you may not be able to take advantage of all features of the Service if you do not.

_Information Others Share_. [We may also receive information about you from other people who use the Service and submit or post content about you in a forum or message board].

_Web Tracking Information_ : Gobza and its third party service providers may use web tracking technologies, such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags and clear GIFs, to collect data related to usage of the Service, the Vouchers and web and email marketing conducted by or on behalf of Gobza. Such data may include the address of the websites you visited before and after you visited the Service, the type of browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, what pages in the Service you visit and what links you clicked on. In order to collect Web Tracking Information and to make your use of the Service more efficient, we may store cookies on your computer. Gobza and third party contractors engaged to provide services on behalf of Gobza (“Contractors”) may also use web tracking technologies that are placed in web pages on the Service or in email communications to collect information about actions that users take when they interact with the Service or such email communications. Web Tracking Information is not correlated by Gobza to individual users. Some Web Tracking Information may include data, such as IP address data, that is unique to you. You may be able to modify your browser settings to alter which web tracking technologies are permitted when you use the Service, but this may affect the performance of the Service.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**

 _Personal Information_ : We will use and store Personal Information to deliver the Service to you, to deliver Vouchers that you purchase, to market the Service to you, to improve our products and services, and for the internal operational and administrative purposes of the Service.

_Aggregate Information_ : We will also use Personal Information to create aggregated data for analytical purposes. This statistical information does not contain any Personal Information and is used to understand our customer base and to better serve our market.

_Web Tracking Information_ : Gobza uses Web Tracking Information to administer the Service and to understand how well our Service is working, and to develop aggregate, statistical information on usage of the Services. This allows us to determine which features visitors like best to help us improve our Service, personalize your user experience, and measure overall effectiveness.

_Email Communications_ : If you create an account and provide your email address, we will send you administrative and promotional emails. If you wish to opt out of promotional emails, you may do so by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the email, or by editing your account settings as described below. All users receive administrative emails. If you wish to opt out of administrative emails, you must delete your account entirely and cease use of the Service.

**What Information Do We Disclose to Third Parties?**

_Public Disclosure_ : Gobza is a publicly available marketing platform where Merchants and other users may upload content in their use of the Service. Any information or content you post using your account will be viewable by other users, and in some cases, may be viewable by the general public.

_Personal Information_ : Gobza does not sell or rent its mailing list, and we will not disclose your email address to any third party for marketing purposes. Gobza will disclose your Personal Information to third parties only in the following limited circumstances:

(i) to Contractors who are performing marketing services, delivering goods, administering promotions, analyzing data and usage of the Service, processing credit card payments, operating the Service or providing support and maintenance services for the Service, or providing customer service. We use reasonable efforts to enter into agreements with all Contractors that require Contractors to use the Personal Information they receive only to perform services for us; and

(ii) when we have your consent to share the information.

_Web Tracking Information_ : We disclose Web Tracking Information to third party advertisers and advertising agencies, [Merchants,] and Contractors, in order for Gobza and such third parties to analyze the performance of the Services and the behavior of users, to operate and improve the Service, and to target advertising to users. We may also publish this information in order to promote the Service.

_Aggregate Information_ : We may disclose anonymous, aggregated information to third parties such as potential business partners, [Merchants,] advertisers, and funding sources, in order to describe our business and operations.

_Network Operators_ : Use of the Service may involve use of the services of third party telecommunications carriers and service providers (such as the services of the carrier that provides cellphone service to you). Such carriers and service providers are not Gobza's contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of the Service is not “Personal Information” and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Gobza is not responsible for the acts or omissions of telecommunications carriers or service providers.

_Additional Disclosures_ : Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, Gobza reserves the right to use or disclose Personal Information and any other information Gobza collects in connection with the Service (a) to any successor to Gobza's business, including as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale or similar transaction, (b) to any law enforcement, judicial authority, or governmental or regulatory authority, to the extent required by law or legal process, or (c) if in Gobza's reasonable discretion, such use or disclosure is necessary to enforce or protect Gobza's legal rights or to protect third parties.

**Privacy Settings/Opt Out**

If you would like your Personal Information permanently removed from our database, please contact us at [info@gobza.com](mailto:info@gobza.com). We will promptly delete your account and you will no longer receive email from Gobza. Your removal from the mailing list or database will not remove records of past transactions or delete information stored in our data backups and archives. Data on past transactions and data stored in backups and archives will be deleted in the normal course of Gobza's business. 

**Access and Updating of Information**

Gobza is happy to allow you to review or amend your email address or contact details held in our database, at any time. Please contact us by sending an email to: [info@gobza.com](mailto:info@gobza.com) or by using your settings panel in your account online.

**General**

_Facebook Connect and Twitter_ : If you log on to the Service using Facebook Connect or through your Twitter account, you agree that any identifying information obtained by us by reason of your connection using Facebook Connect or your Twitter account will constitute Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy, and you consent to our use and disclosure of such information in accordance with this Policy. If we stop using Facebook Connect or Twitter accounts as an access mechanism, you agree that we will nevertheless retain any Personal Information in accordance with this Policy.

_Security_ : We use reasonable security precautions to protect the security and integrity of your Personal Information in accordance with this policy and applicable law. However, no Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that security breaches will not occur. Without limitation of the foregoing, we are not responsible for the actions of hackers and other unauthorized third parties.

_Links_ : The Gobza website may contain links to other websites. Gobza is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our website, and review the privacy statements of each third party website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Service.

_Amendments_ : Gobza may modify or amend this policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, as determined by Gobza, in the way in which Personal Information is collected, used or transferred, we will notify you of these changes by modification of this Privacy Policy, which will be available for review by you at the Service. Notwithstanding any modifications we may make, any Personal Information collected by Gobza from you will be treated in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time information was collected, unless we obtain your consent otherwise.

_Children_ : Gobza does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed at persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use the Service. If Gobza learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 18 years of age has been collected, then Gobza will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. To make such a request, please contact us at [info@gobza.com](mailto:info@gobza.com). 

_Service Visitors from outside the United States_ : LevelUp and its servers are located in the United States and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of the United States. If you choose to access or use the Service, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this privacy policy and subject to such laws.

_Privacy Policy last updated_ : [June 29, 2012]
